Gone Nutty is a animation, adventure, comedy film directed by Carlos Saldanha.
Scrat tries to finish his rather large collection of
acorns when things start going nutty.
Scrat (voice), played by Chris Wedge.
Gone Nutty (also known as Scrat's Missing Adventure) is a 2002 American
animated short film directed by Carlos Saldanha for Blue Sky Studios.
The short features the character Scrat from Ice Age, who is yet again
having troubles with collecting his beloved acorn.
It was debuted on November 26, 2002 on the Ice Age DVD and VHS.
This film was shown in theaters with Garfield: The Movie in 2004.
The film was nominated for the 2003 Academy Award for Best Animated Short Film.
The film explores themes of squirrel, ice age, short film, acorn, absurd.
The tone is lighthearted.